Kettle and Idol
I'm going to ask you to face the screen for the main project, title-cool-cute.
Yes. My three main elements.
Yes.
Now it's time for you to introduce the three key elements that make up yourself.
Let's get to know our guest idols better.
Now, please present your three key elements.
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
Here they are.
I see.
May I read from the first to the third?
Yes, the first one is idols.
And the second one is that I don't have any friends.
And the third one is the staff sample.
Staff sample
I have been an idol since I was in the third grade of elementary school. So this year, I have been an idol for more than half of my life,
I have been an idol for more than half of my life.
I have been an idol for 11 years now.
I've been an idol for a long time, and I've noticed that I've been able to accumulate a lot of idol experience,
For myself, I feel that I cannot live without it,
I think that my life is about idol time,
It occupies that much of my life.
I see.
Is there a particular reason why you became an idol?
Yes, I do. What made me become an idol?
I experienced the Great East Japan Earthquake,
When everyone around me was living in Nanjo,
I felt that the adults around me were smiling in front of us, but not from the bottom of their hearts,
I felt, at a very young age, that although the adults around us smiled in front of us, their smiles were not from the heart,
I wanted to be able to bring smiles to people's faces,
That's when I started to be an idol,
Among idols, I was very strongly attracted to Momokuro-san, and I think it was the first time that I was able to smile so sincerely and normally.
Seeing Momokuro.
Then, when I was allowed to see a live performance of KONAGAWA,
I was scouted by Stardust,
That's how I became an idol.
I see.
So that's how it is.
Do you sometimes go to see idols to introduce yourself?
Yes, I do.
My mother used to like idols a lot,
That's right.
So she used to take me to see them a lot.
I wasn't interested in them at first,
I wasn't interested at first, but I was allowed to go see them,
Then my mom told me that she would be happy if I became an idol,
That was the beginning.
I see. If I said I wasn't interested at the time, I wouldn't have been able to hear any more idol names, would I?
That's how it was.
How do you feel about doing it yourself?
I was in the opposite position.
As an idol.
I am amazed that people smile when they see me having fun,
I myself am saved by the smiles on everyone's faces,
I am also saved by the smiles of others, so I would like to devote my life to bringing smiles back to everyone.
I would like to spend my life giving back smiles to everyone.
That's a good word, isn't it?
Did I just say something good?
Just a little bit.
I'm so sorry.
It's just as you said.
I just said "pearls.
I forgot.
I've spent my life smiling back at you all.
I'm glad I did, because I've had a lot of really great support from you guys, and I've come a long way.
Wow.
Well, that's great... it's nice to hear that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Mu also said that she probably doesn't have any friends.
Oh, he said that!
I see! Yeah, it's some kind of déjà vu, me!
This show is...
Kogesaka-san
Karen's Maimai
Mr. Yamauchi
Karen-kun's Yakiso-Pachi-pachi Panic
Ryuya-san
Thank you very much for your support!
Thank you for all the power!
To all of you
Seinoone, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, eight, nine, ten
power
you